in tooth of great uncertainty the ability to keep calm
在不确定的牙齿上保持镇定的能力
it is and necessary luxury the actions to fix this inch low of with for
这是必要的奢侈行为，它的作用是将这一英寸固定在较低的高度
city ​​but instead i managed to end you while continuing dep or
城市，但我却在继续下沉或结束时设法结束了你
virtually ftp you can find the memoirs or any zhan's store i marcus aurelius
几乎可以通过ftp找到我的回忆录或任何詹的商店
that light as meditation between you is troubles performing is duty
你们之间的冥想是麻烦，这是责任
without losing it might and how old falling for the seductive trap off
而不会失去它的力量和诱人陷阱的下降​​年龄
indulging and sensual pleasures like many other and birth date is our an
和其他许多人一样，沉迷和感性的享乐和出生日期是我们的
english misery is rubert in fair and e-motion this
英语苦难是公平和电子动议的鲁伯特
correct arizer periods or the rest is gravel or hate and silent
正确的点火器时间，否则剩下的是砾石或仇恨而保持沉默
of hostility and oppression and more so in motion scratcher round course
敌对和压迫，在运动刮擦器中更是如此
infecting is already nice fires de marlies or there is the power of stoicism like 'not'
传染已经是好事了，或者像“不”一样有坚忍的力量
and change and of circumstances but for defining or even so weekend deal with
和变化以及环境，但是对于定义，甚至是周末处理
her circumstances no matter how to severe
她的情况无论如何严重
in stoicism we can find the necessary wisdom to become more resilient
在坚忍中，我们可以找到必要的智慧来变得更有弹性
not only to maintain a and also advise to rise and shine in times of
不仅要保持活力，而且还建议在
uncertainty [Music]
不确定性[音乐]
what is not the event that the sturgeon boss store istambul death will agree
如果the鱼老板商店的伊斯兰堡死亡不会达成共识，那该怎么办？
that in regards to the human experience and nothing that is exactly the mind
关于人类的经验，没有什么是真正的思想
even though i may feel and it's the external world that is set up says it's
即使我可能会感觉到，这是建立在外部世界上的，这是
actually do we think about the world that's the jump outside circumstances
实际上，我们是否认为世界是外部环境的跳跃
directly influence our ideas and basically sitting on trigger what live
直接影响我们的想法，基本上坐在触发什么直播
hidden in the subconscious mind like deeply rooted beliefs or perhaps
隐藏在潜意识里的东西，就像根深蒂固的信念，或者也许是
rest experiences so something quiet fits the mind that create the
休息的经历，所以安静的东西适合创造
experience for example we believe that wouldn't face hardships
例如，我们认为不会遇到困难
like these for financials at bax or that we shouldn't software and read in a
像这样的财务财务工具，或者我们不应该软件阅读
lover form that may be unfortunately this means that were still
不幸的是，这可能意味着爱人形式
in the novel of the reality of nature unpleasant events
在自然的现实小说中，令人不快的事件
have a twelve was and the 0s and the right to be excluded from the universal wise
有十二个是，0和被排除在普遍智慧之外的权利
of change according to do x we ​​lift joyce the flow of life the
根据做x的变化x我们欢欣鼓舞生命的流动
aging or al buddy's is where the cissé at arms to control stoicism
衰老或“哥们”是控制独裁者的顺式疗法的地方
emphasizes that the spite of this with your half agency
强调尽管有您的半经纪人
week in format pinions week and george weekend act
小齿轮周和乔治周末法
for example you can lose the on one that only good [ __ ] happened to you
例如，您可能会失去只发生在您身上的糟糕狗屎
accepts that for a moment the most catastrophic events of humanity
接受了一会儿人类最灾难性的事件
my fairybell a pair of pope from a story point of view this should be a
从故事的角度来看，我的仙子是一对教皇
source or celebrate what an opportunity to accept
寻找或庆祝接受的机会
reality and step persisting the inevitable
现实与步骤坚持不可避免
the salon leads to inner peace is a meter away and we bracing for that happened
沙龙通往内心的和平只有一米之遥，我们为发生的事情做好准备
and knowing that not the event what would be an experience is what course how
知道不是这个事件，那将是一种经验，是什么过程
i feel to most things have happened before
我觉得大多数事情以前都发生过
like most creatures on her way you may have limited view on how to live and
像大多数生物一样，您对生活和生活的看法可能有限
photos for great part so limited feel the sites love
照片很大一部分让有限的感觉网站的爱
experience the world take for example a mayfly
体验世界，例如一只may
the key creature is born and d different so creature 1000 new
关键生物是天生的，且与众不同，因此新生物1000
by night 1000 new builds seasons doesn't know
到晚上1000个新版本的季节不知道
by earth and decades is vision of the world is very narrow
地球和几十年来对世界的视野非常狭窄
meaning that thinks it en counters so once in a lifetime experience '
意思是认为它是一生中唯一一次反击的经历，
Charon's armourdillo is mainly the universe shows itself was in
夏隆（Charon）的盔甲主要是宇宙表明自己在
cycles and the waves and ms would like to at least once a chloé
周期和波和女士想至少一次
what happens to was themes and president at wat luc net history lucifer motif en
发生了什么事？沃特卢克网历史路西法主题中心的主题和总裁
met de sturgeon boss and frighten as he already happened before or spend a mix
遇见了st鱼老板，并因为他之前已经发生的事情而感到恐惧或混在一起
natural disasters metalsub stripes traveling to attack
自然灾害metalsub条纹旅行攻击
each other the conservative forces progressive my people the struggles off
彼此的保守力量使我的人民奋斗起来
to interfere with erin api's what how oil after eden some old news
来干扰艾琳·阿皮的事
papers to discover that who is archetypes expressions of all ages that who offers him
论文发现谁是提供给他的各个年龄段的原型表达
even over and over again he is a marcus already here is the look
甚至一遍又一遍，他是个马可，这里已经是样子了
at the best and bar succeeding empire and from deed to extrapolate future
处于最好的状态，阻止成功的帝国，从行为到未来的推断
so a catch no escape from rhythm of events which is why on service life
因此，无法逃避事件的节奏，这就是使用寿命的原因
of forty years is as good as a thousand should you religion anything new and quote
如果您信仰任何新事物并引用，那么四十年的生命就和一千年一样好
3 or wrong argan oil liable the mind is a power for biological
3或错误的摩洛哥坚果油责任心是生物的力量
machine that is capable of turning fantasy into reality ar ability to think
能够将幻想变成现实的机器和思考能力
is the reason why he's a 5 in a world that softens a hall style
这就是为什么他在世界五分之一的水平上会柔和大厅风格的原因
he is in headset by many animals de rafi cycles much stronger than your de
他被许多拉菲动物圈套着，比你的强得多
mind created the most beautiful piece of art
心灵创造了最美丽的艺术品
literature architecture and bright eyes to the moon and will eventually bring
文学建筑和明月的眼睛，最终将带来
a chair other planets it's a powerful tool a bit older out what
一把椅子，其他行星，这是一个强大的工具，
they're a dangerous to explore and possible outcome scambio good thing met
探索它们是危险的，可能遇到的结果Scambio好东西遇见了
when you about duet who get stuck in the mails tram or access or thinking what
当您遇到二重奏而陷入电车或访问或思考的问题时
the strypes inner peace with some possible scenarios over and over again
反复的内在和平与一些可能的场景
canker sore and be there all your rational and beast an assumption how worry about the
溃疡疮，您所有的理性和野兽都存在一个假设，即如何担心
future about all the terrible things that could
关于所有可能发生的可怕事情的未来
have she is very well possible that there could be pictures to forge and what stands out
她很有可能会伪造照片吗？有什么特别之处吗？
is just off but it's not real the manue is not the mail week and drove the
即将结束，但这不是真正的问题，不是邮件周，而是开车
my new fashion times it became quiet a thousand compare to the food on a plate
我的新时尚时代与餐盘上的食物相比变得安静了一千
sb engine stoic castle it we sophomore or te in and with chinese ben
sb引擎stoic城堡，我们大二或与中本
in reality for adversity can make a stronger
在现实中逆境可以使自己变得更强大
terrible idea is that record frisomat jury
糟糕的主意是唱片陪审团
right well marcus aurelius how that disagree with such a statement
很好，马库斯·奥里留斯（Marcus aurelius）如何不同意这样的说法
after all it is a great war still alive and able to arrive after all his
毕竟这是一场伟大的战争，仍然活着，并且能够在他所有的战争之后到达
bintro stones is a boat education
Bintro Stones是一条船教育
live what edging being mentally destroyed the cause of life
生活在精神上摧毁了生命的根源
we would keep this is easier said than done
我们会保持这说起来容易做起来难
that forms stifle mindset how student focus on how bad
形成窒息的心态学生如何集中精力看多糟糕
funkstar the moment a how i get to them and maintain a piece i do like this
funkstar就是我如何到达他们并保持乐曲的那一刻，我这样做
every minute we spend on feeling about your situation and assisting
我们每分钟都会花时间了解您的情况并提供帮助
be the game be considered the best old of life's regardless of
被认为是游戏中最美好的时光，无论
what's happening to was that the wind blown experience while in the morning
发生的是早晨的时候刮风
cycling the marley after you sarlacc mussels and the stronger baby come one who
在您撒了贻贝贻贝之后，骑着马利，而更坚强的孩子来了，
is he at the times and his opportunity to create strict white step suspension them
是他当时的时代，他创造严格的白色台阶的机会使他们中止了
and embrace them in cities die quote is unfortunate that this has happened
并拥抱他们死在城市里不幸的是，这种情况已经发生
well once fortunate and this has happened and ivory means and shapes by the wet
好幸运的一次，这已经发生了，象牙的手段和形状被湿了
chaired by the president of from that of the future
由未来的总统担任主席
5 de president is all i have compared to you mens
与总统相比，我所能做的就是5位总统
animals sint u live much more i media i think i know this all animals experience
动物们，你活的更多了，我的媒体，我想我知道所有动物的经历
4wonders danger that airflow the sgp do this while n that anymore
4奇怪的是，气流可能会由sgp这样做，而n不再
the art of flight of fight and go on living as if nothing happened after
战斗和继续生活的艺术，仿佛之后什么也没发生
word how to know us on the other hand cream and
单词如何了解我们另一方面奶油和
ethan past events for a lifetime and three site ns time or perpetual war ii
过去一生中经历过的事件，以及三个地点的时间或永久性的战争ii
and til death liberace as we let our memories bring back next to whoever lets
直到死亡自由，因为我们让我们的回忆回到任何让
words were meant as well and reality there is another happening that is wrong
话也很有意义，而现实中还有另一件事是错误的
to sign new with present that we jaffrey from
用我们从杰弗里（Jaffrey）的礼物签下新礼物
lori andrews chinese so 1000 mille that poor richard in sheet
洛里·安德鲁斯（Lori Andrews），中国人如此千千，可怜的理查德
it on that we should never and in between bite Lyme for the future
因此，我们永远都不应在未来之间咬莱姆
it's just that the past and future channel to tachos because they don't i seerd
只是tacho的过去和未来渠道，因为我不明白
studies is another lines let the presence is all that port
研究是另一条线，让存在是所有的端口
what should I do with the situation cleanliness will have lot less to worry about six
我应该如何处理环境清洁度，而不必担心六个
word tying anyway from the moment were born on life and taking away second
从那时起，无论如何，这个词都会在生命中诞生并夺走第二名
after second des is an in level pour conséquence of
在第二次浇注之后
life and at the same time the most destructive it can be
生活，同时最具破坏性的是
and then he was since the disintegration
然后他自解体以来
and and annulation or what s repressive or even
和环空或什么压抑甚至
scm castle the front wheel sticking arms when look forward to death the major
scm城堡的前轮在期待死亡时粘着手臂
portion of there has already passed whatever you baby else there is in their
那里的一部分已经过去了，无论您的孩子，他们的其他地方
hands and quote live that's what this sing-along journey is for
双手并现场报价，这就是这次唱歌之旅的目的
full of surprises what waist of time to spend your life's and take away and to
充满惊喜的是度过一生的时间来度过自己的一生，带走和去
resist and towards whom a counter is nicely busy
抵制柜台正忙于谁
creating this falls sense of security called the very nature of
创造这种下降的安全感被称为
the universe is in security mood this they were being is can of
宇宙处于安全状态，这是他们可以的
stupid is how I sort the item or shapes
愚蠢的是我如何排序项目或形状
perspective it makes more sense to standard time though
角度来看，这对标准时间更有意义
remember that all time here is ltd loes and softgrip of the past and future
记住，这里一直是过去和未来的有限责任和软实力
week en cissé de day while maintaining in european
周日在欧洲进行维护
7 in the grunts germ of things were not that important even worse still overlay
咕germ咕germ的东西中的7个并不那么重要，甚至更糟的是，
occupied by anxiety and specially and times of certainty food of life's
充满焦虑，特别是和确定的时光
in perspective salt remember the myfly for millions
在透视图中，盐记住了数百万的苍蝇
perspective the life of the mayfly comes across is a savior in significant on
透视may蝇的生活是一个重要的救世主
current what for the 1700 years altri with isola di everything tree in the world
当前1700年的altri与isola di世界上的所有树木
human life i chose construction he distri here even although many
人类生活我选择了建筑，尽管许多
inch and straw x and units life time management civilizations
英寸和稻草x和单位寿命管理文明
or comb and god for me suze la de un lifespan
还是梳子和上帝对我来说是生命的延续
is one that much well comprend des to the history of art planet and then put too
是对艺术星球历史非常了解的作品，然后也
planet in the perspective of the cosmos now we've been reduced to almost nothing
从宇宙的角度来看行星，现在我们几乎沦为零
so 1000 min that the young and experience thousand count for gifted we through billet i
如此一千分钟，年轻人和经验丰富的千人算是我们通过方坯获得的天赋
to experience the place which is a beautiful thing
体验美丽的地方
richard les oversize and lifespan which mean kick you off the ball or
理查德·莱斯（Richard les）的身材过大且寿命长，这意味着您无法踢球或
how mind or even whether wood fancy a live actually yes you might realize that many
究竟有多大的心态，甚至是否看中了某人的生活，您可能会意识到很多
of the small and i van beek things were born about way they mean next to nothing
小东西和我范贝克的事物诞生于它们几乎意味着什么的方式上
a hundred years of nou last league of your interest in pudding
一百年来你对布丁的浓厚兴趣
stole it philosophy into practice you might want to check out the playlist
偷偷把哲学付诸实践，您可能想看看播放列表
story exercises for inner peace thank you for watching
内心和平的故事练习谢谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]